http://www.jaani.net/privacy

AboutMeContactWeblogCategoriesLinklogSearchContributeLawLaw NotesJudicial QuotationsPhotographyVisual DiaryGalleryAbout the DiaryVisual Diary ArchiveEquipmentResourcesLinksWordsMultimediaArtFlash Games
Home
Privacy Policy
Summary
This page is long and boring, so I’ll make it simple:
I am not a spammer.
I will not sell your details to spammers.
I do collect some personal information so you can use the website.
But I don’t do anything bad with it.
I honour all your rights under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
You can contact me if you’re at all concerned or curious about privacy matters.
There, that wasn’t so bad, was it?
Now get back to browsing the site.
If you must, the full text of the Privacy Policy appears below.
General principles
Privacy is a fundamental human right.
This website respects your privacy wherever possible, and complies with the National Privacy Principles set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (Privacy Act) and general duties prescribed by the Spam Act 2003 (Cth) (Spam Act).
What personal information is collected?
From you
If you become a member of Jaani.net, you will provide some information during signup (username, password, email address at a minimum).
The username is publicly displayed and will appear on the site wherever you post comments or other files, and possibly elsewhere.
The password is encrypted at the moment you type it — I never see it and can’t get access to it (I can only reset it for you).
It’s encrypted pretty well and, while not unbreakable, should be fine.
Your email address is never publicly displayed unless you make it so.
You can also provide some optional information in your member profile.
This information — your university, favourite case, judge, day job, and so on — is basically a fun way of interacting with other members.
You can write whatever you like.
However, you should be aware that it will be displayed on your profile page to other members and the general public.
If you rate pages, your username will be recorded as having entered a vote (so you can’t vote twice).
However, it won’t normally be displayed to me or publicly, so you’re quite able to bad-mouth the content without me knowing.
If you post comments then, obviously, your username is displayed alongside the comment, and anything you write will be visible to the general public.
Be sensible and don’t write your email address in plain text.
From your computer
The web server upon which Jaani.net is stored will record certain data when you access this website.
Those data include:
Your internet protocol address;
Your internet service provider’s domain name;
Your User Agent; and
The date and time of your access request.
This site also uses Google Analytics to gather some basic and anonymous information about your computer (browser, operating system — that kind of thing).
I use this to see how many people visited the site (ego-boosting, in other words) and make decisions about which browsers to support, and so on.
Nothing to be alarmed about.
The login system sets a persistent cookie — just like Google, Facebook, MSN and Yahoo — so you don’t have to login every time you visit.
Cookies are harmless and can be disabled if you prefer.
How is that information used?
Your personal information is used to grant you access to this website (eg, to process your login details and show you content set in your user preferences), to make your browsing experience more useful or fun (eg, rating content, showing you articles you haven’t seen yet), to help me fine-tune the site (eg, to tell me what the most common screen resolutions or web browsers are) or for a specific purpose that will be obvious when you supply the information (eg, to print your comment!).
Optionally, you may let other members contact you via your user page.
They won’t see your email address — it’s kind of similar to Facebook’s wall feature.
So, information may also be used to enable this functionality behind the scenes.
When might that information be disclosed to others?
There are essentially three cases in which some or all of this information could be disclosed to a third party:
When I have toCoercive legal processes — such as a subpoena, discovery or otther court order — or substantive legal obligations may mean that I have to hand over (inter alia) access logs that include your personal information;
When I choose toTo avoid serious harm to myself or a third party, I may choose to disclose personal information to an extent reasonably necessary to avert that harm;
When something goes awryCyberspace is a wild west; technology is imperfect; people are cunning and egotistical; these ingredients combine to make Bad Things happen in cyberspace occasionally.
If my web server is hacked, or your transmission is decrypted, then your personal information may inadvertently be disclosed to a third party.
Although I will take reasonable steps to secure the web server, I can’t take responsibility for everything — especially things that go wrong during transmission or on your computer.
To this end, any information you send me is sent at your own risk.
How can you access information stored about you?
In the first place, you should try to use your user preferences page to alter your privacy options to settings with which you’re comfortable.
If you want something else, send me an email and I’ll respond with the information forthwith if you’re entitled to it.
Print
Members
Log in using OpenID:
What is OpenID?
Glyndebourne and the warmest day of summer #opera #england...Linklog
Picnic at Glyndebourne before Janacek’s Cunning Little...Linklog
A sunny wander through Pembroke College, Cambridge #sunshine...Linklog
Pembroke library #cambridge #pembroke #college #uni #camuni...Linklog
A charming Cambridge laneway #street #england #cambridge...Linklog
Delightful weekend in Cambridge: Pub dinner at The Granta #pub...Linklog
